http://www.aesica-pharma.co.uk/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
This block is broken or missing. You may be missing content or you might need to enable the original module.
Privacy policy
1. Introduction
Recipharm AB and its affiliates (“Recipharm”, “we”, “us” or “our”) are committed to protecting your privacy as a customer, website visitor or other third party, such as a contact person of a company or other organisation which we collaborate with. This policy aims to explain how we collect and use your personal data in accordance with applicable data protection legislation as well as how you can exercise your rights.
If you have any questions or requests relating to this privacy policy, the processing of your personal data or who is the data controller in a specific situation, please contact us using the contact details set forth in section 11.
2. What information is collected and for what purposes?
Purpose
Categories of personal data
Legal basis
Administer our relationship with you and/or the company you represent, e.g. to be able to:
communicate with you;
respond to your inquiries and requests;
send invoices and, if necessary, send reminders;
keep statistics of sold products;
address any questions regarding products; and/or
maintain contact lists.
General information and contact details, such as
Name
Address
Phone number
E-mail
Employer and title.
In some cases we may also process social security numbers.
Legitimate interest
The processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interest to administrate the relation between us and the company that you represent.
Fulfil our legal obligations, e.g. in order to comply with accounting and/or tax legislation.
Financial data such as:
Bank information
Credit/debit card information
Other information about any transactions carried out between you and us that is required under applicable law.
Legal obligation
The processing is necessary to fulfil a legal obligation that is required from us, e.g. through mandatory legislation.
Send you marketing communication, invitations to events and surveys by post, e-mail or similar technology.
E-mail
Address
Name.
Legitimate interest
The processing is necessary to send marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you.
Provide you with online services and/or e-mail notifications when you register/subscribe to our website.
E-mail
Address
Name.
Legitimate interest
The processing is necessary in order to provide you with the services that you have requested.
Use data analytics to study how visitors use our website in order to improve the website.
Technical data, such as:
IP-address
Geographical location
Browser type
Referral source
Length of visit
Number of page views
Other information about how you use our website.
Legitimate interest
The processing is necessary in order for us to improve and create a more user-friendly and secure website.
In addition to the personal data that you provide to us, we may collect information from third parties, e.g. your employer, an information services company, an authority or other public registers.
If you do not provide certain information when requested, we may not be able to perform a contract we have entered into with you, use our services we provide on our website and/or be prevented from complying with our legal obligations.
We will not use automated decision-making or profiling and we will only process your personal data for the purposes stated in this privacy policy. Should we process data for any other purpose than what we collected the personal data for, we will inform you accordingly.
3. To whom is your personal data disclosed?
In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:
to company’s within our company group to the extent required to fulfil the purpose of the processing of your personal data;
to our service providers who may only process the personal data on our behalf;
to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
in connection with any legal proceedings or potential legal proceedings;
in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights(including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
We will not sell your personal data to third parties.
4. Where is your personal data located?
Information that we process about you may be stored and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate, in order to enable us to use your personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.
Your personal data may be stored and transferred to countries which might not necessarily have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area (“EEA”). However, we will take all reasonable technical, organisational and legal measures to ensure that your personal data is securely processed, providing an adequate level of protection compared to the level of protection offered within the EEA.
5. How is your personal data protected?
We will take adequate security measures to prevent any accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure of, or access to your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
6. For how long is your personal data saved?
We will only save your personal data as long as necessary in order to achieve the purpose it was collected for or as required in order to comply with retention periods under applicable law.
To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we will considers the amount, nature and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which the personal data is processed for and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.
7. What are your rights and how can you exercise them?
7.1 Right to access your data
You may instruct us to provide you with a copy of the personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information is generally free of charge but may under certain circumstances be subject to the payment of a fee.
7.2 Correction, deletion and restriction
You may request us to correct any incorrect information we have about you as well as to delete any information that is no longer necessary for the purpose it was collected for and/or to restrict processing of your personal data under certain circumstances. However, certain legal obligations may prevent us from immediately correcting, deleting and/or restricting certain information.
7.3 Data portability
Under certain circumstances, you have a right to receive any personal data that you have provided to us and to have the personal data transmitted to another data controller.
7.4 Recall your consent
If we process any of your personal data based on your consent, you may recall your consent at any time.
7.5 Opt-out from marketing
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes. You can also instruct us not to use your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time.
7.6 Lodging complaints
You may lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority at any time if you are of the opinion that we process your personal data in breach of applicable data protection legislation.
8. How are links to third party websites managed?
The website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy does not cover the links within this website lining to other third party websites and we are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other third party websites.
9. How does this website use cookies?
You can read about how we collect and use cookies in our Cookie policy.
10. When is this privacy policy updated?
We keep this privacy policy under review and we may update it from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
This privacy policy was last updated 12/09/2018.
11. How do I contact Recipharm?
Please contact us by using any of the below contact channels:
Recipharm AB (company reg.no. 556498-8425)
Box 603
101 32 Stockholm
Sweden
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +46(0)8-602 52 00
12. Who is my data controller?
Recipharm AB is usually the data controller for the processing of your personal data. However, in some situations Recipharm AB and its affiliates are joint data controllers or an affiliate is the lone data controller of your personal data.
Each company is listed below, and if you wish to identify the controller for any specific situation, please use the contact details as set forth in section 11.
Recipharm AB
(company reg.no. 556498-8425)
(company reg. no. 556695-5752)
(company reg. no. 556666-2606)
(company reg. no. 556662-4366)
Box 410, Björkbomsvägen 5
691 27 Karlskoga, Sweden
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +46 58 668 200
Recipharm OT Chemistry AB (company reg. no. 556761-5439)
(company reg. no. 556666-8231)
Mariefredsvägen 35
645 41 Strängäs, Sweden
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +46 8 602 52 00
Recipharm Pharmaceutical Development AB (company reg. no. 556825-0095)
(company reg.no. 556666-8249)
Bränningevägen 12
120 54 Årsta, Sweden
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +46 8 602 52 00
Recipharm Venture Fund AB (company reg. no. 556666-2697)
(company reg. no. 556731-7226)
Lägervägen 7
136 50 Jordbro, Sweden
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +46 8 602 52 00
Recipharm Ltd.
(company reg. no. 8174784)
Vale of Bardsley, Ashton-under-Lyne
Lancashire, OL79RR, United Kingdom
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +44 161 342 6000
Lusiomedicamenta Sociedade Técnica Farmacêutica S.A. (company reg.no 507150473)
(company reg. no. HRB5875)
Herderstrasse 2
83512 Wasserburg, Germany
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +49 8071 1008 0
Mitim S.r.l.
(company reg.no. 07047730150)
Via Cacciamali, 34
25125 Brescia, Italy
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +39 030 349 761
Liosintex S.r.l.
(company reg.no.01690860158)
Via Mantova, 8/12
20020 Lainate (MI), Italy
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +39 029 372 032
Edmond Pharma S.r.l.
(company reg. no. 00804270155)
Strada Statale de Giovi, 131
20037 Paderno Dugnano (MI), Italy
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +39 029 100 111
Biologici Italia Laboratories S.r.l.
(company reg. no. 01233940467)
Via F. Serpero, 2
20060 Masate, Italy
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +39 029 500 461
Recipharm Kaysersberg Pharmaceuticals S.A.S.
(company reg. no. 813 689 213)
23 Avenue Georges Ferrenbach
68240 Kaysersberg, France
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +333 89 78 76 00
Recipharm Fontaine S.A.S.
(company reg. no. 509 186 169)
(company reg. no. B-87899001)
(company reg. no. B-65 376 055)
C/Ramón y Cajal, 2
08150 Parets de Vallès, Spain
E-mail: privacy@recipharm.com
Telephone: +34 934 629 800
